[
    {"question":"What does CPU stand for?","correct_answer":["Central Processing Unit"]},    
    {"question":"What does RTX stand for?","correct_answer":["Ray Tracing Texel Extreme","Ray-Tracing Texel Extreme", "Ray-Tracing Texel Xtreme", "Ray Tracing Texel Xtreme"]}, 
    {"question":"Who is Team Blue?","correct_answer":["Intel"]},
    {"question":"Who is Team Green?","correct_answer":["Nvidia"]},
    {"question":"What is Asus' gaming brand called?","correct_answer":["ROG","Republic of Gamers"]},
    {"question":"RAM: Random __________ Memory","correct_answer":["Access"]},   
    {"question":"How many GB are there in a Terabyte?","correct_answer":["1000","1000GB", "1000 GB", "1000","a thousand","thousand","one thousand","1024","1024GB", "1024 GB"]},   
    {"question":"Which part of a computer is responsible for connecting all the parts togetherF?","correct_answer":["Motherboard"]},
    {"question":"Which manufacturer makes the chips for most flagship Android devices?","correct_answer":["Snapdragon","Snap dragon"]},
    {"question":"What programming language is used to develop apps for iOS, MacOS and other Apple operating systems?","correct_answer":["Swift","Swift 5"]},   
    {"question":"Windows 11 introduced a new taskbar. What was different about the alignment?","correct_answer":["It was centred","In the centre","centered","centred","In the center","it was centered"]},
    {"question":"The popular single-board computer manufacturer, Raspberry Pi, was originally made to teach coding to who?","correct_answer":["Kids","Children"]},
    {"question":"What is the name of the mini micro controller made by the BBC?","correct_answer":["Micro:Bit","micro bit"]}, 
    {"question":"What is the name of the AI Nvidia made which transforms a rough, terrible outline into a piece of landscape art?","correct_answer":["Canvas","Nvidia Canvas"]},
    {"question":"Which screen type did PlayStaion Vita have?","correct_answer":["OLED"]},
    {"question":"The Gameboy, Gameboy Color and Gameboy Advance screens weren't liked very much because they had no __________.","correct_answer":["Backlight"]},   
    {"question":"What does AMD, the semiconductor manufacturer, stand for?","correct_answer":["Advanced Micro Devices"]},
    {"question":"eMMC storage is described as being the soldered version of what external storage device?","correct_answer":["SD Card","Secure Digital Card"]},
    {"question":"What specification is used to mount NVM Express drives to a motherboard?","correct_answer":["M.2"]},
    {"question":"What type of mechanical keyboard switch is preferred by gamers as it is highly responsive?","correct_answer":["Red","Red switch", "Cherry MX Red", "Cherry MX Red Switch"]},
    {"question":"How many cores does Ryzen 9 3900X have?","correct_answer":["12","Twelve","12 Cores","Twelve Cores"]},
    {"question":"What is the maximum amount of RAM an Apple Mac Pro can be configured to have?","correct_answer":["`1.5 TB","1.5TB", "1.5 Terabytes", "1500GB", "1500 GB"]}
]